[sighs]
What now, Zaikahal?
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
EVIL X AND X TERRIBLE
[narrator] His name is Gyro,
the NGL's shadow don.
[narrator] Gyro spent
the first 12 years of his life
until Gyro finally killed him
and made his escape.
It was incredibly rare
for him to talk to Gyro,
who slept on the upper bunk.
It was for that reason
he barely knew how to speak
before he was seven years old.
When Gyro returned from work,
he was not permitted to leave his bed,
and only before 9:00 p.m.
The rotting wood of the bed frame
would creak loudly
whenever he would turn in his sleep.
-[creaking]
-[narrator] His father hated that sound.
Once, that noise caused his father
to beat him severely,
and after that, Gyro learned to sleep
without moving a muscle.
He also learned
to hold his bladder at night
and kept an empty liquor bottle
by his bedside
for when he simply
couldn't hold it in any longer.
learning from his mistakes.
His father had never bought him anything,
not even a toy,
Inside his small, troubled world,
his father was essentially a god,
and no matter how cruel
his father could be,
Gyro continued to idolize the man,
believing that deep down,
his father truly needed him,
a belief stemming from two facts.
When Gyro was five,
he suffered a terrible fever
that nearly killed him.
His father stayed up all night,
replacing his towels with fresh ones.
The other reason was that his father had
never at any point ordered him to leave,
not even once.
And these two facts
filled Gyro's young heart with pride.
You idiot!
You know why your dad
hasn't kicked you out yet?
It's just because
you still bring in money.
[narrator] Though he had
previously kept that possibility
locked away deep in his mind,
when the older youth
brought it to light so harshly,
something in Gyro snapped.
His pride gravely wounded,
a feeling of rage overcame him,
and he attacked the youth.
[spoon clatters]
to the point where not even
knocking Gyro out would satisfy him.
He stomped on the boy's face, spat on him,
and then he uttered the finishing blow.
When you got sick,
it was a neighbor who took care of you!
Bet you didn't know that, did you?
Your dad didn't lift a finger for you.
He asked your dad
what he would do if his kid died,
and do you wanna know what he said?
It wouldn't matter.
I don't care if he lives or if he dies.
That was when Gyro finally understood.
-[drink pouring]
-No one cares if I live or die,
not even my own father.
In other words, my life has no meaning.
if I live, I'll bring in money.
if I die, I'll free up space in the room.
That's all.
but I know now
that the only reason he said that
was so he could avoid
any inconvenience for himself.
Those words
were never meant to help his son.
'Others' meant my father.
No.
It meant 'humans.'
Eventually the boy stood up,
and he grabbed a nearby hammer.
Nine years later, Gyro founded the NGL,
which became a nation
nine years after that
with him as its king.
The drug DD was merely the first step
in achieving that greater goal.
[scoffs] I didn't feel like fighting them.
The food will reach the Queen either way.
Gyro, huh?
Damn it. I should have just eaten him.
Listen up. I'm taking over this factory.
From now on, this is my fortress!
-[gunshot]
-[birds screeching]
[gunshots]
[laughing]
[gunshots and laughter echoing]
Hang on.
Exactly what the hell is going on here?
Actually, one of my own
has gone totally missing too.
Its communications have been cut off,
and it hasn't returned yet.
Yunju's team
dealt with all the humans holding guns.
Now, how would I know that?
Probably some brand-new weapon
that we haven't seen yet.
I can tell because the bullets
are still lodged inside of the body.
I'm not so sure about the others.
It appears the skull was punctured.
It said one human mimicked firing a gun,
and although no projectile emerged,
something pierced the soldiers' skulls,
killing them.
So they possess
a number of abilities we do not.
These humans
may be tougher than we thought.
[scoffs] If it's a human power,
then I'm sure we can learn to use it,
since we've inherited those traits.
It's not a big deal.
You don't understand.
The humans' real strength
lies in their ability to learn things.
Yes, I suppose you do have a point there.
Who in the world is Reina?
Uh, I didn't say it. You did.
that are capable of defeating
our foot soldiers.
[sighs] What do we do?
Only soldiers of our rank
can use complex weapons,
but humans are fortunately
not aware of that fact.
That will definitely frighten them.
[Peggy] I see.
Reina, huh?
[bees buzzing]
[Ponzu] It's no use.
No one received the message.
So the other Hunters we were
in contact with are probably dead.
I see.
Let's go.
Those creatures are too much
for us to handle.
We need to get out of the NGL
and tell the whole world
what's happening here,
then form an extermination team.
Fine! Whatever!
Let's just hurry up and get out of here…
[sighs]
[body thudding]
[gasps] It's…
Come on! More will be coming soon.
-[Pike] Hold on.
-[all gasp]
I thought I instructed you
to capture the humans alive, didn't I?
We're supposed to deliver them
to the Queen while they're fresh.
Wait. That's a human face.
But what is that thing?
[Balda] Fire! Open fire!
ORANGE ARROW
[Pokkle] My Orange Arrow is the fastest
of my Seven Spectrum Array Rainbows,
and he caught it easily.
[Balda screaming]
Balda!
[Balda screams]
You bastard!
Wait. One moment, please.
My hands are full.
You're pathetic in battle,
but that's hardly unusual.
the nutritional value
of a thousand normal humans.
Well done, Pike. Good job.
[Pike swoons]
[gasps] Mistress Zazan!
I am ever so grateful for your praise.
You honor me.
[Ponzu] I can't save him myself.
I have to call for help.
There might still be time.
Even if they take him,
they probably won't eat him right away.
Please, take this to the Hunter
with the strongest aura you can find.
I have to get back to the border
as fast as I can.
This is so much fun.
[chomping]
Hunting is so much fun.
HELP!
CHIMERA ANT NEST
ROCKY AREA
NOTIFY HUNTER ASSOCIATION!
-[Kite] It'll be risky.
-[boys gasp]
You sure you want to come along?
Yeah.
We're professionals, aren't we?
Miss translator,
I'm sorry, but we really must hurry.
Right.
I'm sure the horses can gallop
a bit faster if it's necessary.
-They still won't be fast enough.
-Huh?
I want you two to return to the border
and rendezvous with the others.
Then call the Association.
These things are dangerous.
Got it.
You be careful, okay, Kite?
I will.
Keep up, or I'll leave you behind.
Yep, and right back at you.
Let's go.
[stammers]
This is a bullet casing.
But I thought anything mechanical
was forbidden here, isn't it?
It means the underground rulers of the NGL
weren't only manufacturing drugs,
but weapons.
Yeah, but judging by this…
[Kite] This wasn't a human.
Most likely, it was a Chimera Ant.
If my instincts are correct
and the Chimera Ants
are using firearms now…
I hate to say it,
but it's possible
the NGL's underground rulers
have already been fed to the Queen.
What would happen if the Chimera Ants
were born with their genes?
The NGL and the Chimera Ants,
it's the worst combination imaginable.
This will be an unprecedented biohazard.
[narrator] The situation has taken
a sudden turn for the absolute worst.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "The Fight Begins."
Ready, set, Gon!
[grunts]